Hunger Action Network of New York State; Records apap161
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Research & Subject Files, 1973-2000, Undated; 6; 4.5 cubic ft.
  - Welfare Employment, 1998-1999 (Box 3 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Welfare Employment System, 1998 (Box 3 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Welfare Evaluations and Quizzes, 1990; 1996; Undated (Box 3 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Welfare, Family Violence Option (FVO), 1998 (Box 3 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - "Welfare Made a Difference" National Campaign, 2000 (Box 3 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Welfare Medicaid, 1999; 2000 (Box 3 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Welfare Monitering, 2001 (Box 3 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Welfare Mothers LaDonna Pavetti, 1997 (Box 3 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Welfare News, 2001 (Box 3 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Welfare Pataki Bill, 1996 (Box 4 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Welfare Polls, 1996; 1999-2001 (Box 4 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Welfare Privatization, 1988; 1996-1997 (Box 4 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Welfare Rights, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 4 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Welfare Reform, 1985-1987 (Box 4 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Welfare Reform, 1987-1989 (Box 4 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Welfare Reform, 1990-1992 (Box 4 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Welfare Reform, 1990 (Box 4 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Welfare Reform, 1993 (Box 4 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Welfare Reform, 1994 (Box 4 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Welfare Reform, 1999 (Box 4 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Welfare Reform, 2001 (Box 4 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Welfare Reform Congressional Profiles, 2000 (Box 4 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Welfare Reform Immigration, 1997 (Box 4 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Welfare Reform and Jobs, 1997 (Box 4 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Welfare Reform and Jobs, 1998 (Box 4 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Welfare Reform, National, 1995 (Box 4 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Welfare Reform, National, 1996 (Box 4 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Welfare Reform, National, 1996-1997 (Box 4 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Welfare Reform, National, 1998 (Box 4 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Welfare Reform, National, 2000 (Box 4 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Welfare Reform, New York State, 1995 (Box 4 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Welfare Reform, New York State, 1996 (Box 4 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Welfare Reform, New York State [1 of 2], 1997 (Box 4 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Welfare Reform, New York State [1 of 2], 1997 (Box 4 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Welfare Reform, New York State, 1998 (Box 4 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Welfare Reform, New York State, 2000 (Box 4 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Welfare Reform, Postsecondary Education, 1998-1999; 2001-2002 (Box 4 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Welfare Reform, Postsecondary Education, 1998-2001 (Box 4 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Welfare Reform, Watch Project, 1999 (Box 5 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Welfare Reform,The Welfare Reform Act of 1997 (Box 5 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Welfare Reform Studies, 1998; 2000; 2001 (Box 5 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Welfare Skit Preformed by HANNYS, Undated (Box 5 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Welfare Safety Nets and Caseloads, 1999; 2001 (Box 5 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Welfare Senator Daniel Moynihan, 1995 (Box 5 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Welfare Task Force, 2001 (Box 5 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Welfare: Temporary Assistance for Families (TANF), 2000-2001 (Box 5 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Welfare Transportation, 1997-1998 (Box 5 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Welfare Transportation, 1997-1998; 2000; 2002 (Box 5 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Westchester County Funding Request, 1997-1998 (Box 6 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Workfare, 1994-1995; 1998 (Box 6 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Womens Leadership Project, 1994-1996; 2000 (Box 6 (6-Research & Subject Files), Folder 3)